International news:
Two pandas named
"Yuanyuan" and "Manman",
They were transferred to Noah's Zoo.
located in the Noah Islands three years ago,
They recently gave birth to a baby panda.
According to statistics issued by
Alliance platform for global broadcasting
I have an extraordinary little panda
Now over 700 million followers.
In the past, we've seen pink pandas
A brown panda and a panda
without black fur on the back.
All of these are very rare heirlooms
Genetic is uncommon
A panda with two black
eyes of different sizes
Very rare in the history
of animal genetics.
This little panda is unique
.of its kind in history
We're making progress, sir.
We can buy it.
truly?
They are just asking an inflated price.
Just pay them.
Don't you think about it first?
Regardless of the cost,
I will pay.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
As required,
The goods will be delivered to you
.on time
Good! Stop filming!
you guys?
Are you okay?
Yes
Well done, guys
Hey, take those wires down.
Don't let her falter.
..that's really it
original!
1 against 30 people.
This is wild!
Let's go! Applaud for Jackie!
Yes!
All sections! Come on, hurry up...
In re-shooting location
They filmed this again.
Filming this again?
We've done it many times. to stop.
Let's take a break!
The CEO will buy us
Milk tea!
This is unbelievable!
I single-handedly defeated an entire mortal squad?
Am I a superhero?
It's a commercial film.
It should be entertaining,
-Isn't that?
- Yes, yes, yes.
You are so smart and wonderful!
.I will play a romantic role in the next movie
amazing!
Boss, I just wrote the "Love" trilogy.
Part One, “Love Under a Rain of Bullets.”
-It looks like an action movie again.
Part two...
Sorry. It's a short circuit.
What is the title of the second part?
Part Two.
"Love in the pool of blood"
If so,
What is the title of the third part?
love..."
"Love in whatever."
Let's sign this trilogy contract.
Don't you know the rules?
You must know her, right?
Who are you to ask for a break?
If I don't ask for a break, what will I ask for?
Filming finished today?
What's next on my schedule?
International Arctic Competition
...for all-star golf
They invited you for the opening
I'm not going to the golf tournament.
Good.
An invitation from Mr. Stallone.
To attend the new house party
At his place of residence
no. Send him flowers instead.
Good.
The first ice festival in
..South Africa “your request”
To cut the ribbon at the opening ceremony.
Ice festival in South Africa?
Maybe it's man-made ice.
Of course not, if it was made by man.
Good.
Ocean Film Festival in
Somalia invites you to attend its opening...
Somalia"?
Let's get past that.
.Seems a little dangerous
Noah's Zoo invites you to adopt a panda.
Panda?
this.
So it's him?
The largest star animal in the world.
-It's so beautiful!
-Are you going?
Oh my God!
Sorry.
He's really cute.
"Kung Fu Star (Jackie) Pandaman"
"Jackie adopts a panda."
"Jackie announces adoption of a panda."
Welcome distinguished guests.
- Hello.
Welcome to Noah's Zoo!
Thanks.
I'm the manager here. I'm Peter.
You can call me Old Bay.
-Can you speak Chinese?
We have a lot of Chinese tourists.
This is Anastasia, my assistant.
- This car is here.
-Is this your car?
- Yes.
From this direction.
Thanks.
"Noah's Zoo"
Look, your fans.
From this direction.
Thanks.
Look here!
-You can't eat this.
-Why?
It's too sweet.
Your blood sugar level!
But why did you buy two?
Because the second one is half the price.
Hey, you can't eat that either.
It's full of fat!
my lord.
Hot dogs, please
Come on, come on, come on.
I took a bite out of this!
|| Panda Plan ||
Hello, Amy.
- Hello, Tony.
-You are beautiful today.
Hello, Sherry.
- Hello, Tony.
You are beautiful in uniform.
Make room for the robot.
Hello, Tony.
I'm working. Please step aside.
I'm working.
Hello, Chuchu.
You look beautiful today.
No, you're not talking to me again.
Your meal has arrived.
You big baby.
Get down, you big baby!
If you don't want it, I'll drink it.
Can you come down to save face?
You big baby!
Drink and I'll leave.
Get down, you big kid
Good.
You have to make me work
Late, aren't you?
Welcome.
Can I have ice cream please?
naturally.
Did you see Jackie today?
Yes.
Are his bowed legs clearly visible?
- Yes, very clear!
What about his nose?
big! I'll tell you something.
His nose covers half of his face.
I missed a lot.
I didn't see him today. Thanks.
Mr. Jia.
Are these your remains?
It's so stinky.
You never pay.
Don't ask for that much.
By the way, I can't afford it
..looking at you as if you were...
You have never seen the world before.
What if he was a star?
What are you looking at?
Don't think I'm just an ice cream seller.
I'll tell you something.
I used to work in Hollywood.
I sell ice cream.
There were a lot of stars.
(will smith)
Keanu Reeves, Tom...
Tom...
And Jerry.
We know each other well. Am I bragging?
I take this with open arms. truly.
- Hello.
This nose also covers half of his face.
Ice cream please.
Welcome.
- (Jackie Chan).
- (Jackie)!
It's Jerry, not Jackie.
Jerry is an American mouse.
Jackie is Jackie Chan.
He's from Hong Kong.
(Jackie)!
It's really Jackie!
Oh my God! (Jackie Chan)!
Boss! (Jackie Chan)!
Take a picture.
Boss! Can we take a picture?
Go get the phone
Hello
-Can I sit here too?
- Yes, please.
-Thank you.
Mr. Jia is a very arrogant man.
I can't finish this.
Let me give you some
no. I eat ice cream here every day.
- Really?
- Yes, there is no need.
-I am the panda nanny, Su Xiaozhou.
- Panda nanny?
I'm here to adopt...
-I know. I know that.
I've watched the news.
Can I ask you?
A few personal questions?
no.
I'm just kidding. Ask.
How rich are you?
Next question.
How many friends did you have?
How rich are you?
Other questions other than these two
Ask me anything else
President.
I've just improvised a masterpiece for you.
Try it
-She's beautiful. Thanks.
- Thank you, boss.
-Thank you.
Thanks.
Try it, there will be a lot.
- No, no, no.
There is still a lot. Don't let him go.
There will be more.
I don't want!
I can't finish this!
Relax, Mr. Jia!
that it...
He is very hospitable.
-This is too much for me.
Why don't we go somewhere else?
Want to see a panda?
-Can I?
- Of course.
Come on, let's go!
I'll enjoy this later.
"air cleaner"
You big baby?
Is his name "Big Baby"?
What a random name.
It's a random name.
My pet's name is "Big Baby".
You big baby.
He's so naughty.
He's hiding again.
-You big baby!
You big baby.
What is this?
He surprised me.
..his maneuver is
Hugging feet.
Can I hug him?
Yes.
-He likes you.
- How do you know?
Because he will fart.
how...?
How did you know he was going to fart?
He just relaxes once in a while
He sees someone he likes
When he calms down, he farts.
It is truly exceptional!
Good.
Our men are on the island now.
Boss, we have received the deposit.
Customer wants delivery in
.as soon as possible
Hey buddy.
Trust in Chaikon.
It will be a pleasure to work with you.
(James)! (James) (James)!
Who wants to go to the zoo?
calm!
Hello boss.
We are elite mercenaries.
Why would we kidnap a panda or something?
For your sake.
We're going to be a laughing stock in this business, right?
You will be a joke.
But this joke...
Its value is 100 million dollars!
Come on, come on!
Good try.
"Panda House"
Now, brother.
I don't sleep well these days,
But I don't know why, man.
truly?
I feel like I have no appetite at all.
I don't want to eat anything.
This is really strange.
But at least the situation is calm today.
Not hungry at all.
But at least work is easy today.
(Harry)!
I'm stuck!
Screw it
Get down here quickly!
I'm stuck!
the curse!
"Guards of your safety"
Boss.
Surveillance cameras have been turned off.
...We came together to create this sanctuary
Exceptional wild animals.
"Panda Adoption Conference"
Now Noah's Zoo,
In the open ocean,
It belongs to all of humanity.
-Do you know her?
No
Why wave to her if you don't know her?
I will get to know her soon.
I would like to take this opportunity to thank Ronald.
Adopt our little pandas
"Yuanyuan" and "Manman"
And also Jackie for adopting the panda
Our famous little one
Gentlemen, if you can sign
On the baby panda's adoption certificate.
- Of course.
- Here you go.
Thanks.
Yes, yes.
I'm at the conference with Jackie.
How many times have I told you?
Single, I'm single.
I am single now.
Not what you think.
I remember the last time I felt nervous,
Specifically when receiving an Oscar.
Welcome.
...Very happy and honored to adopt a baby panda
If you want to take a picture with Jackie,
-I can help you.
-Thank you. I took a picture.
If you want it signed...
I got it too.
So if you want...
I promise..
I will do my best to take care of him.
Let's hope this little panda grows
Strong and healthy.
"Internal control room"
“Panda Hall.”
Naming a baby panda is very important.
Let me think about this, okay?
Thanks!
All cameras have been turned off
Surveillance in the panda's house.
All exits are closed.
This is the only way out.
Pass card, guys.
Boss, an unexpected problem has just occurred.
Panda adopters
A famous movie star...
- Let's move!
He never listens to you, man.
Look at that.
Isn't it nice?
You can take pictures.
Is this panda similar to the one you have?
Who's cuter?
Panda or Jackie?
Welcome?
In general, you can take more photos
- Hello?
Hello
I am happy to serve you.
You need guidance...
- Hello!
- Back off!
Move!
Back off!
- Don't move!
- Back off!
Get down!
On your knees!
- Ladies and gentlemen!
- What's going on?
Don't panic.
We are not here to hurt anyone.
We're here for Baby Panda.
But...oops.
- Whatever happens, call the police.
-I will do it!
“Internal control room, Noah's Zoo
Don't move!
- They went down!
On your knees,
Do you hear me?
Don't move!
How dare you!
I'm the manager here!
I won't let you take even a pig
Wild is one of the two zoos
Not to mention the panda!
Are you serious?
Well, wild boars
Fine is negotiable.
-Is this...?
This is Jackie!
(Jackie)?
What is he doing here?
Step aside!
They went down!
Move!
- Move!
- They went down!
Move!
Back off!
They went down!
Can this star?
Cinematic combat really?
Yes. He's brilliant.
His kung fu fighting is really cool.
truly?
We'll see about that.
We'll see about that!
how's it going?
- Did you call the police?
-There is no signal.
No signal?
Carry it first.
Let me check what's going on.
Jackie...
Is this really you?
Yes. I'm Jackie Chan.
Good.
Where is the baby panda?
Panda?
- In this direction.
-Bring him
Be careful. He's very weak.
Yes, leader.
Why do you need a baby panda?
-Who are you guys?
- Can you really fight like in the movies?
I'm just a kung fu star.
Let's go!
Come on now!
- Come on!
- That's nice!
Don't mess around, Jackie.
Stop!
Loading...
Begin intensive cleansing.
You are brilliant.
Your hand is on me! I can't fight.
I'm just a movie producer.
I just...
Friend, okay? Leave me.
Good.
Sorry.
- Just an accident
.. -You
You have no arts ethics
Self defense.
-Can you speak Chinese?
I know all these tricks, Jackie.
I've watched all your movies.
Can't escape? I got you now.
Wait...wait.
Why do you want to fight?
We have to do this, Jackie.
Good.
.in this case
I am waiting.
I think it's better here
here.
Do you see?
The ring. The ring.
Come here!
Good.
Let's go!
This isn't in the movies, Jackie. Get up!
Where are you going?
Stop, stop.
Good?
You won! I give up!
give up! Don't come close!
Don't come close!
Do you want this?
Take this!
I'll whip your ass! Take this!
I will flog you!
Take this...!
I'll whip your ass!
Take this! You deserve this!
Take more!
I'll whip your ass!
You lied!
You said you can't fight!
You also have no morals
Martial arts
I will kill you!
This is me. Enter here.
Come in.
The door is there. Come in.
Come in
Bump your head!
Have you seen a panda?
.no. I didn't see him
What's going on inside?
I don't know.
Suddenly a gang enters to kidnap the panda.
Call the police!
-There is no signal!
No signal.
It's not your fault.
I'm with you.
I will protect you.
(Harry)?
Did you see anyone?
No
Don't let him get away, okay?
Yes.
(Harry).
nothing.
no.
.it's all over
Welcome.
to stop!
- Stop!
You!
You idiot!
- Stop there!
I'm not good at hitting people.
But I'm good at taking hits!
the curse.
Don't move.
How can I move?
Don't get up.
Is this a good place for you, Jackie?
Let's go.
Good.
Why is he so hard to fight? the curse!
Let's go.
Close the door!
Shut it!
Hurry, hurry!
What should we do?
Are you asking me?
If not you, then who?
You?
I can't help it.
I am not familiar with this place.
“Tony.”
- (Jackie Chan).
I am your biggest fan!
- Who is this?
- It's the Noah Island robot.
My name is Tony.
I'm on my way.
Hello handsome.
Can you let me pass?
Brother, can you let me pass?
-There is no way!
Let me find him!
They are coming!
Let's go.
Come on, come on!
Come on, don't be afraid.
There is no road ahead.
-There is no road in this direction.
- Get up here!
It's a tall building! No, no, no!
I can't do it!
Don't be afraid.
I...
I'm just a panda nanny!
Just imagine it's flat land.
Walk as if it were flat.
-It's flat! It's flat!
- Yes, yes!
Don't look down!
Where is this headed?
that it...
-It's like a dead end.
Come on
Let's go.
- Come here.
Where are we going?
Let's jump from here.
What?
There is no turning back.
The cartoon panda will support you. Believe me.
-I don't believe you.
Boss, I'm just an ordinary nanny.
I'm not your risk taker.
Let's jump to the count of 3.
-I don't want to try!
1!
Are you well?
car. Get on!
Where should we go?
.- Seat belt
Go. Go!
Where to now?
- Go!
They escape in a panda tourist car.
Look for them!
They entered the storage area.
It is out of the range of surveillance cameras.
James, they're headed
To the storage area.
It's very heavy.
Boss. You have a connection.
Oh leader
Jackie suddenly appeared and took the panda.
- Jackie?
- Movie star.
Tell James, you'd better...
To bring back the panda before I get there.
Let's go to the sidewalk.
I woke up.
I woke up. I woke up.
Don't be hasty.
Hurry!
Come on guys!
What?
Borrow your weapon.
Let's go! Jump!
I'm coming!
Leave me!
Everyone, get out.
Find a safe place to hide.
Let everyone follow me.
From this direction.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
I will fix the means of communication
And ask for help
What about you, David?
I'll look for Jackie.
good.
Your car's engines are running very slowly. Why?
All our equipment here is slow.
Maybe for safety.
- He's gone.
- Look for him!
-You big baby!
You big baby!
You big kid
-You big baby!
You big baby?
(Su Xiaozhou).
- (Su Xiaozhou).
-Did you find him?
Look at him.
He sleeps like a baby.
He must have eaten too much
He ate all of it.
Does it taste good?
no.
Check your phone signal now.
Yes.
I think they took control of the central control room.
Wow.
This place is not safe then.
Don't bring us bad luck.
locomotive.
Take cover.
Is there another way out?
Yes, there's a side door from there.
Good.
Go when I tell you to go.
- Ready?
here.
Don't shoot any of you, you bastards.
We want them alive.
Good
The door does not open.
Can't you open it?
What's wrong with your mouth?
Don't worry.
Come on, come on.
Screw it.
Climb.
locomotive.
Get on my back.
Can I do it?
Yes, do it.
Good.
The stairs.
No, it's the elevator.
Good.
He's coming down.
"Translated by: Dr. Ali Talal! Fouad Al-Khafaji"
Oh my God.
It's like in his movies.
I have to take some pictures.
You idiots, do you want an autograph or something?
Leader.
What should we do?
Jackie goes up again.
Who the hell chose the elevator?
Don't move, Xiaozhou.
Watch the panda.
Don't say anything.
I'm afraid of heights.
Panda, panda.
Quickly, quickly.
Jump now.
Smart.
I am amazing.
Where will you throw me?
Jump.
Big baby.
Know.
Are you well?
(Xiaozhou).
Didn't you run away?
How can I escape if you can't?
What a waste of our time.
(Jackie).
Give me the panda.
I'll give you the panda and you can set it free.
Good.
He didn't say anything.
No no.
Stay where you are.
(Roy).
Bring the panda.
I?
Don't be afraid, big baby.
beware.
You're just like in your movies.
It's beautiful.
And soft.
pistol.
Don't move.
I've never shot a real gun before.
Did you shoot?
Just to scare them.
The more I fear, the more they fear too.
Relax.
Well, I'm relaxed.
Where is your gun?
Big baby.
Get out of my way.
Boss, you sent the big kid...
Noah filling machine.
"Fresh packaged meat"
Big baby.
Not you again.
no.
You move very slowly.
Come and help me, boss.
I am trapped.
Save me, boss.
Don't move.
I'm tied up.
I can't breathe, man...
Stay glued to that.
Everyone ordered to lower their weapons.
Everyone lower their weapons.
He put a gun to my head.
Quickly or I'll blow your head off.
Listen to him.
His gun shakes in his hand.
(Xiaozhou).
Throw their weapons away.
"Tony."
Hello, Chuchu.
Lend me a helping hand.
It's up to me if it's important.
I'll shoot.
Hurry up!
In the box.
Say it.
Hurry up!
Put them in the box.
I don't like working late.
Go as far as you can.
(Xiaozhou).
Go with Tony.
The three of us will leave.
Boss, take care of yourself.
I'm going, boss.
I can't do it, boss.
Get her out of the way.
They released her.
Hurry up!
Let's go.
I'm going, boss.
Leader.
He has no weapon.
No weapon?
Don't move.
Get me out of here.
What should I do?
"Operator's Manual: Electric Forklift"
Raise your hands.
Don't mess with my station.
President.
I'm coming to save you.
I will kill you.
President.
Give me a moment.
There are three words I don't know.
move"
Boss, I'm coming to save you.
I'm here to save you.
Come on, boss.
You almost killed me.
Sorry.
Ride.
Get on board immediately.
That's a hundred million dollars, you idiots.
Screw it.
Can you do it?
Hold on.
Oh my God.
Where are we going?
It's a wrong way.
Do you have a driving license or not?
to stop.
Get in the car.
Director.
We started evacuating visitors from the island.
Let's locate them.
How long will it take to restore our connections?
They damaged the primary communications power unit.
It will take time for it to be ready
To work with all his energy again.
So hurry up.
Director
Look.
Let's check out the panda.
He's fine.
They are following us.
They turned around.
They are coming.
They are right behind us.
Come on, come on.
Blue hair, boss.
He's trying to catch me.
Hold me tight.
President.
Hold on to the pandas.
Are you okay, boss?
President.
Help me, boss.
He's coming.
President.
You'll be fine, big baby.
Don't be afraid.
Help me, boss.
Are you okay, boss?
Leave driving.
No problem now.
relax.
Keep cameras trained on cars.
faster.
They turned around.
no.
What is this?
Oh my God.
Put me down.
Screw it.
faster.
Give me the panda, boss.
Catch them.
They're coming for us, Boss.
I know that.
Our path ends.
Open the gate.
The gate opens.
Quickly, quickly.
Don't let them escape.
Learn, leader.
Wait.
Hold the button.
Close the gate.
immediately.
Why is the gate closed?
Wait patiently.
Let's go.
Let's stay close.
Okay.
They did it.
Stop screaming.
The gate is closed.
"I entered the wild beast's territory."
This should be the easiest task.
Someone open this gate now.
Well done.
Gate...
There is someone to help us.
the boss.
He must be the manager.
The manager is in the central control room.
there.
We are safe now.
"Wild beast area, do not get out of the car."
President.
We're safe now, right?
What do I know about that?
In fact, the situation is more dangerous now.
We ran out of fuel.
No fuel?
How are we running out of fuel at this time?
Is it my fault?
Screw it.
What's up?
lion.
Screw it.
What's up now?
He's hungry.
He is hungry like a lion is hungry.
Get him something to eat.
Don't let him whine again.
He only drinks milk at this time.
milk?
Is this milk?
President.
Is rhino milk beneficial?
I think so, they share with the cow
The same name in Chinese is "Nu".
What do you think of the snail called "Wanu"?
Close your mouth.
Who will go?
Don't scream.
Not me.
no.
President.
Run without me.
Did you say you're a failed athlete?
Are you turning your back on me?
They took over the sidewalk.
No ship will pass.
Make sure we follow a schedule
To feed animals accurately.
Director.
Okay everyone.
You better get out of here now.
And find a safe place to hide.
What about you, director?
I?
Do you know what I was before I became a manager?
I was deputy director.
there.
Don't move.
Okay, okay.
Good.
Welcome.
Director.
Please, open the gate.
It pleases me.
Screw it.
Sorry, you'll have to find that out yourself.
Is this all you have?
You coward.
We have no choice but to burn the door.
Search carefully. Don't let them run away.
- Your order, sir.
- Sure.
And now there are wild animals
Or mercenaries in these mountains.
Be careful.
What should we do?
here.
This lighthouse was abandoned long ago.
No one from the outside knows about this.
Electricity box.
Watch out, boss.
What's up?
What are you doing?
There was a spider there.
Be calm.
Slow down, boss.
Hold it.
Catch the panda.
I'm not sure if there's a risk.
I'll check first.
President.
The place is safe.
Go up.
Leader.
Our men are still searching.
But this place is very big.
We have additional men to search the area.
Search the whole area.
You will search there.
And you are with me.
Good.
Is it over?
Okay.
Thank you, President.
What do you thank me for?
I am his adopter.
It is my duty to protect him.
Why did you bother with the panda?
I love him.
When I was in elementary school, I went
To the zoo on spring break.
I was impressed when I saw the pandas.
In college, I studied zoology.
When I'm on vacation I like to go
To the panda sanctuary as a volunteer.
I have worked and spent time with pandas.
For a full period of five years.
When I think about it, it's like a dream.
Will you do this forever?
"letter of resignation"
Are you going to resign?
My parents wanted me to quit.
They are getting older and I hope to stay with them.
Every time I tried to quit, he hugged my legs.
I couldn't take a step.
What about you, President?
You've been fighting for decades
What keeps you going?
What keeps me going?
that it...
"Start shooting."
"Start shooting"?
I remember when I was eight years old
I went to the set and heard
The director says, "Start shooting."
I was young then and did not know what it meant.
But wherever I hear the phrase
"Start shooting" somehow...
I'm filled with intense enthusiasm
And uninterrupted energy.
And then...
“Start shooting” has become synonymous with me.
It is my trumpet and my starting pistol
Before you say “start shooting” I am like all of you
I'm afraid, in pain, and tired.
But as soon as I hear, "Start shooting,"
Then I will become a champion.
Perform any dangerous scene
And he achieves everything.
In an instant, decades passed.
Life is like a dream.
But one always wakes up from the dream.
So when do we wake up?
Stop that and go back to sleep.
President.
Boss, don't forget to give the panda a name.
Okay.
What a great name?
Help me.
And give me ideas too.
It's easy to name a panda.
For example...
"pingping", "anan" = security.
"Jagao", "Xinxing" = happiness.
"Mimi", "hoho" = astonished.
They seem to be asleep, as if dazed.
Let's call one "meme" and the other "hoho".
Panda "Hoho".
This is a great name.
Let's go.
Move!
there.
They are at the top.
It's noise.
Catch them.
There is someone here.
Let's go.
Let's get moving.
There's someone here, boss.
I wake up.
Nobody arrived.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
Don't let them run away.
Catch them.
Boss, we have them.
We got them, boss.
We have to send them to the ship.
Come back and I will talk to them.
Leader
They are here.
How is my panda?
He was vomiting and not eating anything.
You.
Take care of my panda.
maybe...
I let you live.
Let's go.
What should we do?
But Jackie...
So keep him here.
The ransom must be huge.
Well, let's go, baby.
Let's go.
No no.
I will meet...
to stop.
As for you...
Power in the sea.
Okay, boss.
no.
Get moving!
Let's go.
No, please.
no.
Let's go.
Come in.
Big baby.
Give me a minute, you big baby.
I'll get you out right away.
Come on, come on.
It's your last meal.
Eat it.
Eat fast and go.
Are you still alive?
What do you think?
Surprised you?
You surprised me.
These two.
These are my two buddies now.
(Harry).
(Roy).
He is the great president.
President.
What is this about?
No no.
I can give you both money.
I will give you more...
no.
No no.
please.
May I have a life jacket please?
I give you money.
What are you doing?
This is impossible.
Qayani in the sea.
We love.
There is no love.
No no.
We love...
(Jackie).
Yes, yes.
We love Jackie.
Oh my God.
Are you my fans?
Okay.
It's show time.
Show him.
decent.
No, no, I believe you both.
Sit down.
Okay, okay.
There you have it, President.
They're stealing pandas for...
.Sell it to a businessman
But they don't know who the businessman is.
And now once you dock
This ship will be sold to the Panda.
Wow.
What about Xiaozhou?
Find the panda and Xiaozhou immediately.
Can you confirm that communications
Are they all back on the island?
We will leave.
We will meet you tomorrow.
Watch out, young people.
Good.
"High voltage danger"
What are you doing?
Stop.
Move your hand.
Leave him alone.
Take it out of the box.
- Please stop.
- Stay away.
Take it out of the box.
Let's go.
-Stop.
Don't touch it.
Stay here.
Go and save Xiaozhou.
Good.
(Xiaozhou).
I came to save you.
What are you doing?
Stay away from me.
This is me.
Comrades...
It's game time.
Listen.
I'll stay and go with the truck.
You two get out of here immediately.
They called the police.
I'll give you my watch.
Good.
Your watch?
I don't know how to use it.
The president is brilliant.
Leader.
Roy, we trust this guy.
How's our $100 million?
Basically in the car, boss.
Keep going.
They saw me.
You mean these two people?
Don't worry, they are with us.
They are with us now, as they have defected.
What does he mean?
The bike, right?
-Put your hand down.
Good.
What do they mean?
They told us to take the bike and run away.
Don't be afraid, I'll count to three.
One, two, three.
Let's go.
Who will drive it?
Welcome.
Can you ride a bike?
(James).
The police have arrived.
Bring weapons.
Take your defensive positions.
They retreated.
Secure that gate.
The panda was captured.
Wait.
This task was more difficult than we expected.
One hundred million dollars is not enough.
We need more than that.
It's the price we agreed on.
Don't move.
Why are you here?
Give me the panda.
I don't want to hurt anyone.
concept?
Hey butler. The master will return soon.
What's the situation, President?
I'm busy.
Speak up.
The police have located you.
They are on their way now.
I found the huge baby.
Big baby.
Is the big baby okay, boss?
Arrested...
What happened to him?
Big baby.
I mean, I got arrested.
It's okay as long as the big baby is okay.
Boss, the police will be arriving soon.
What did you say?
Just don't give up.
I can't do it.
I can't stand it much longer.
What's the problem?
President.
I can't bear...
Boss, hold on a little longer.
President.
Talk to me, President.
What's the problem?
I am like all of you
I'm afraid, in pain, and tired.
But as soon as I hear, "Start shooting,"
Then I will become a champion.
Perform any dangerous scene
And he achieves everything.
President.
Listen to me.
"Start shooting."
Don't move.
-We are the police.
How are you, President?
Are you well?
Welcome? President?
What's going on, President?
What happened to the big baby?
Welcome? President?
How annoying you are.
I know, how's the big baby doing, boss?
The big baby is fine.
And I'm fine too.
decent.
See you at the pier.
Okay, President...
Are you the one who wants a panda?
Why?
Six months ago...
Pasha was diagnosed with leukemia.
That was when the little panda was born.
Pasha saw him for the first time on television.
Since then we have been going to the park
animal almost every week.
Pasha leaned in front of the glass.
And I looked at the panda all day.
Pasha's condition deteriorated rapidly.
I wanted the panda to stay with her for a while.
Perhaps her health will improve.
She doesn't even know what's going on.
It's my fault.
Oh God...
Please forgive me.
Where is the panda?
Send to the dock.
Sidewalk?
Help yourself.
Am I dreaming?
You are not dreaming.
are you hungry?
Would you like to eat?
He can't drink it.
I'll drink it, okay?
Are you well?
I was waiting to see you.
But I'm sick.
You know? He came to
see you for this reason.
You will be treated, your health will
improve and you will recover soon.
Can I play with him?
certainly.
You can play with him as long as you want.
Later: Panda Sanctuary in Chengdu, Sichuan.
Hello panda.
(David).
Clean the tank, then remove
the panda droppings.
I'm not hungry, boss.
I'll eat it when I'm done.
"Hoho."
Come here.
“(Hoho) has a beautiful appearance and is full of vitality
He likes to stay in the roost to play and sleep.”
President.
We'll fly to Shanghai at 3 p.m.
For cinema events and holidays
Weekend in Milan
To promote your new film.
By the way...
Corgis were owned by
the Queen during her lifetime.
But they were stolen.
The British government called to ask you
If you have any plan to save them.
Okay.
What's your decision?
Plan B for those who have no plan.